Clement F. Haynsworth Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- United States Court of Appeals File, 1955-1989 (Box 6-201)
  - Case File, 1956-1989 (Box 7-159)
    - 1985 October term
      - Dowless v. Warren-Rupp Houdailles, Inc., No. 85-2301
      - Bubla v. Bradshaw, No. 85-2318(L)
      - Barksdale v. International Business Machs. Corp., No. 85-2319
      - Marmott v. Maryland Lumber Co., No. 85-2344(L)
      - Consolidation Coal Co. v. Federal Mine Safety and Health Review Comm'n, No. 85-2369
      - Harlow v. Imperial Colliery Co., No. 85-2373
      - Daniels v. Quinn, No. 85-2403
      - Rook v. Rice, No. 85-4004
      - United States v. Levy Auto Parts, No. 85-5006
      - United States v. Lewis, No. 85-5021
      - United States v. Stewart, No. 85-5046(L)
      - United States v. Fortmann, No. 85-5047(L)
      - United States v. Kennedy, No. 85-5050
      - United States v. Gray, No. 85-5063
      - United States v. Modern Elec. Co., No. 80-5070
      - United States v. Bryant, No. 85-5080
      - United States v. Pansera, No. 85-5095
      - United States v. Fields, No. 85-5107
      - United States v. A-A-A Elec. Co., No. 85-5116
      - United States v. Burnside, No. 85-5119(L) (Box 121)
      - United States v. Cole, No. 85-5152(L)
      - United States v. (Under Seal), No. 85-5156(L)
      - United States v. Tuckson, No. 85-5157
      - United States v. Welch, No. 85-5160
      - United States v. Small, No. 85-5161
      - United States v. Fry, No. 85-5162
      - Allegheny Mut. Casualty Co. v. Russell, No. 85-5185
      - United States v. Bell, No. 85-5190
      - United States v. Turner, No. 85-5206
      - United States v. Sigmann, No. 85-5214
      - United States v. Singley, No. 85-5215
      - United States v. Wentz, No. 85-5243
      - United States v. Ferguson, No. 85-5502(L)
      - United States v. Wright, No. 85-5510
      - United States v. Gallo, No. 85-5513
      - United States v. Adams, No. 85-5537
      - United States v. Aguilar, No. 85-5541
      - United States v. Cooper, No. 85-5577(L)
      - Crowley v. Landon, No. 85-6097
      - United States v. MacDonald, No. 85-6208; (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 122)
      - Griffin v. Virginia, No. 85-6267
      - Ashford v. Edwards, No. 85-6288
      - Renzi v. Virginia, No. 85-6484; (2 folders)
      - Brown v. Newhart, No. 85-6688
      - United States v. Morse, No. 85-6741
      - Wilson v. Secretary of Health and Human Servs., No. 86-1529
      - Hurt v. G. C. Murphy Co., No. 86-2521
      - Brock v. Yost, No. 86-2549
      - In re Gary H. Watts Realty Co., No. 86-381l; (2 folders)
      - United States v. Jones, No. 86-5004(L)
    - 1986 October term (Box 123)
      - Sleboda v. Benefits Review Bd., No. 84-1447
      - Sheckler v. Clinchfield Coal Co., No. 84-1756
      - United States v. Tindle, No. 84-5036
      - Gillespie v. Beatrice Pocahontas Coal Co., No. 85-1016
      - Hicks v. Southern Md. Health Sys. Agency, No. 85-1085
      - Davis v. Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac R.R., No. 85-1151; (2 folders)
      - Harvey v. Director, Office of Workers' Compensation Programs, No. 85-1201
      - Gillespie v. Badger Coal Co., No. 85-1335
      - Brunswick Beacon, Inc. v. Schock-Hopchas Publishing Co., No. 85-1389; (2 folders)
      - Boyce v. Turner & Newall, Ltd., No. 85-1630; (1 folder) (Box 124)
      - Consul, Ltd. v. Transco Energy Co., No. 85-1729(L); (2 folders)
      - Ivy v. Dole, No. 85-1764
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Comm'n v. Ocean City Police Dep't, No. 85-1798; (3 folders)
      - Hines v. IBG Int'l, No. 85-1800
      - Feller v. Brock, No. 85-1912(L)
      - McCoy v. United States, No. 85-1997(L)
      - Virginia Dep't of Educ. v. Secretary of Educ., No. 85-2035
      - Fran Welch Real Estate Sales v. Seabrook Island Co., No. 85-2057
      - Sovran Mortgage Corp. v. FCA Mortgage Corp., No. 85-2124 (Box 125)
      - Heirerli v. Painewebber, Inc., No. 85-2139(L)
      - Gulf Oil Corp. v. Chiodo, No. 85-2150
      - Pension Benefit Guar. Corp. v. Dorsey Corp., No. 85-2166
      - Miller v. Tar Heel Container Corp., No. 85-2171
      - Jones v. City of Richmond, No. 85-2242
      - Khan v. Jenkins, No. 85-2252
      - Polo Fashions v. Craftex, Inc., No. 85-2302
      - Dawodu v. Immigration and Naturalization Serv., No. 85-2313; (2 folders)
      - Chuck's Feed & Seed Co. v. Ralston Purina Co., No. 85-2337; (2 folders)
      - Presidential Gardens/Duke St. Ltd. Partnership v. Slye, No. 85-2353
      - Joyner v. Lancaster, No. 85-2392 (Box 126)
      - Thomas v. Delta Enters., No. 85-2397
      - United States v. Bray, No. 85-5195
      - United States v. Velasquez, No. 85-5217(L)
      - United States v. Colzie, No. 85-5254
      - United States v. Guglielmi, No. 85-5255
      - United States v. Greene, No. 85-5256
      - United States v. King, No. 85-5582
      - United States v. Campos, No. 85-5583
      - McQueen v. Garrison, No. 85-7513
      - Rex Sys. v. Holiday, No. 86-1008
      - Sports Accessories v. Coopers & Lybrand, No. 86-1030
      - Murphy v. Bowen, No. 86-1040
      - Hoover Universal v. Brockway Imco, Inc., No. 86-1043
      - Rhodes v. City of Lincolnton, No. 86-1052
      - Park Corp. v. Lexington Ins. Co., No. 86-1061 (Box 127)
      - Hager v. United States Steel Corp., No. 86-1074
      - Walls v. United States Steel Mining Co., No. 86-1122
      - Sunbeam Corp. v. Equity Indus. Corp., No. 86-1129
      - Federal Election Comm'n v. Caucus Distribs., No. 86-1149
      - Blanton v. Friedberg, No. 86-1158
      - Atlantic Wood Indus. v. Serafin, No. 86-1163
      - Mabry v. Richardson Memorial Dialysis Center, No. 86-1179
      - Lewis v. Bowen, No. 86-1187
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Mattie C. Hall Health Care Center, No. 86-1206
      - Samples v. Director, Office of Workers' Compensation Programs, No. 86-1227
      - Gilliam v. Armtex, Inc., No. 86-1537
      - Johnson v. USS Chem., No. 86-1548
      - Federal Election Comm'n v. Halter, No. 86-1560
      - Johnson v. Flowers Indus., No. 86-1602
      - Monger v. Bowen, No. 86-1617
      - Union Trust Co. v. Charter Medical Corp., No. 86-1645
      - United Guar. Residential Ins. v. Philadelphia Sav. Fund Soc'y, No. 86-1655
      - Foremost Guar. Corp. v. Community Sav. & Loan, No. 86-1662(L); (2 folders) (Box 128)
      - Star Auto. Co. v. Jaguar Cars, No. 86-1684
      - Yadkin Valley Bank & Trust Co. v. McGee, No. 86-1685
      - Alliance Moving and Storage Co. v. Bennett, No. 86-1688
      - Reynolds v. Department of Recreation and Parks, No. 86-1701
      - Russell v. Lufkin, No. 86-1719
      - Carter v. Tisch, No. 86-1728
      - Brewster v. Doe, No. 86-2002
      - Kenny v. Quigg, No. 86-2073
      - Woodhouse v. Norfolk School Bd., No. 86-2095
      - Tarantion v. Baker, No. 86-2109
      - Morse v. The Daily Press, No. 86-2125
      - Ware v. Lawyers Title Ins. Corp., No. 86-2139
      - Hettrick v. Bowen, No. 86-2141
      - In re Micka, No. 86-2159
      - In re Robbins, No. 86-2178
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Granco, Inc., No. 86-2531
      - Robinette v. Director, Office of Workers' Admin. Programs, No. 86-2548
      - Guy v. Travenol Laboratories, No. 86-2553 (Box 129)
      - Warrilow v. Birsch Chems., Ltd., No. 86-2557
      - Novak v. Whitacre, No. 86-2562
      - Felty v. Graves-Humphreys Co., No. 86-2573
      - Bowles v. United States, No. 86-2583
      - Swartz v. Prudential Ins. Co. of Am., No. 86-2607
      - Wheeler v. Bowen, No. 86-2644
      - Corbin v. Bowen, No. 86-2645
      - Wilkins v. Aetna Casualty & Sur. Co., No. 86-2649
      - Long-Airdox Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 86-3010
      - Grattan v. Board of School Comm'rs of Baltimore, No. 86-3021
      - Richland Wholesale Liquors v. Glenmore Distilleries Co., No. 86-3052
      - Liberty Oil and Gas Co. v. Equitable Gas Co., No. 86-3057
      - Todd Transp. Co. v. Provident State Bank, No. 86-3069
      - Boggess v. Adkins, No. 86-3081; (2 folders)
      - Ground Breakers v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 86-3105
      - School Bd. of Richmond v. Bradley, No. 86-3106
      - Whitley v. Celotex Corp., No. 86-3108 (Box 130)
      - E. F. Hutton Mortgage Corp. v. Clott, No. 86-3124
      - Eldridge v. Bouchard, No. 86-3155
      - Entre Computer Centers v. FMG, No. 86-3520(L); (2 folders)
      - Wright Chem. Corp. v. Del Rey Chem. Int'l, No. 86-3564
      - Bowman v. United States, No. 86-3597
      - Rose v. Director, Office of Workers' Compensation Programs, No. 86-3599
      - John Hanson Sav. & Loan v. Maryland, No. 86-3607(L)
      - District 28, United Mine Workers v. Lowlands Coal Corp., No. 86-3610
      - Mobley v. Bowen, No. 86-3640
      - Reinhardt v. Benefit Trust Life Ins. Co., No. 86-3642
      - International Corp. of Am. v. Merrill Lynch, No. 86-3644(L)
      - Arnold v. Bowen, No. 86-3653
      - In re Metmor Fin., No. 86-3710
      - Doe v. Baker, No. 86-3711
      - In re Environmental Coal Processing Sys., No. 86-3716
      - Mid-South Brokerage Co. v. Dak Foods, No. 86-3835
      - Merrikh v. United States Immigration & Naturalization Serv., No. 86-3842 (Box 131)
      - Adkins v. Board of Governors, Fed. Reserve Sys., No. 86-3853
      - Department of the Navy v. Federal Labor Relations Auth., No. 86-3870
      - United States v. $62,950, United States Currency, No. 86-3871
      - Brinderson Corp. v. Hampton Rds. Sanitation Dist., No. 86-3949
      - Clanton v. Bair, No. 86-4002; (2 folders)
      - United States v. Haye, No. 86-5009
      - United States v. Suthard, No. 86-5026
      - United States v. Laroque, No. 86-5040
      - United States v. American Waste Fibers Co., No. 86-5043(L)
      - United States v. Lindh, No. 86-5053
      - United States v. Aders, No. 86-5127
      - United States v. Leung, No. 86-5131
      - United States v. Okolo, No. 86-5176
      - United States v. Fickling, No. 86-5179
      - United States v. Gasque, No. 86-5184
      - United States v. Robinson, No. 86-5532
      - United States v. Aguiar, No. 86-5533
      - United States v. Alpert, No. 86-5534 (Box 132)
      - United States v. Crisp, No. 86-5539
      - United States v. Nichols, No. 86-5540
      - United States v. Addison, No. 86-5544
      - United States v. Gilbert, No. 86-5553
      - United States v. Howard, No. 86-5573
      - United States v. Harris, No. 86-5576
      - United States v. J. Health Care Center, No. 86-5581
      - United States v. Yancey, No. 86-5596
      - United States v. Martin, No. 86-5604
      - United States v. Briley, No. 86-5619
      - United States v. Moore, No. 86-5620
      - United States v. McFadden, No. 86-5628
      - United States v. Jackson, No. 86-5650
      - Williams v. Kelly, No. 86-7281
      - Pierce v. Davis, No. 86-7374
      - Leonard v. Hammond, No. 86-7540
      - Plyler v. Leeke, No. 86-7654; (2 folders) (Box 133)
      - Crockett v. United Mine Workers, No. 87-1049
      - Simmons v. Risher, No. 87-1542(L)
      - Mitchell v. Sea-Land Servs., No. 87-3025(L)
      - United States v. Christian, No. 87-5048
      - In re Grand jury proceedings, No. 87-5051
      - United States v. Taylor, No. 87-5501
      - United States v. Berras-Rivera, No. 87-5511
    - 1987 October term
      - Auer v. Kawasaki Motors Corp., No. 85-1591; (2 folders)
      - ITT Indus. Credit Co. v. Durango Crushers, No. 85-1976
      - Muhammad v. Warden, Baltimore City Jail, No. 85-7005 (Box 134)
      - Island Creek Coal Co. v. Lake Shore, No. 86-1172
      - Beatty v. Chesapeake Center, No. 86-1176; (2 folders)
      - St. Paul Fire and Marine Ins. Co. v. Seafare Corp., No. 86-1183
      - Prudential Ins. Co. of Am. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 86-1199
      - McKenna v. Sovran Bank NA, No. 86-1228
      - Henderson v. United States Fidelity and Guar. Co., No. 86-1259
      - Barzee v. Trammel, No. 86-1264
      - United States v. Stacy, No. 86-1675
      - Lavay Corp. v. Dominion Fed. Sav. & Loan Ass'n, No. 86-1699(L)
      - Taylor v. City Nat'l Bank, No. 86-1715
      - Foster v. Tandy Corp., No. 86-1726
      - Hatfield v. Occidental Chem. Corp., No. 86-2014 (Box 135)
      - Introcaso v. Cunningham, No. 86-2064
      - Central States v. Central Transp., No. 86-2100
      - Grimes v. Owens-Corning Fiberglass Corp., No. 86-2586
      - Mills v. Internal Revenue Serv., No. 86-2598
      - Smith v. Local 7898, United Steelworkers, No. 86-2600
      - United States v. Shelton Coal Corp., No. 86-2606
      - Currie v. United States, No. 86-2643
      - In re Cavalier Court Assocs., No. 86-2661(L)
      - Poling v. Capital Sys., No. 86-2669 (Box 136)
      - Gerber Prods. Co. v. Fisher Tank Co., No. 86-3039
      - Crawford v. College Life Ins. Co. of Am., No. 86-3088
      - Chem-Nuclear Sys. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 86-3111
      - Barrash v. Bowen, No. 86-3123
      - Greene v. Bowen, No. 86-3138
      - Lilly v. Harris-Teeter Supermarket, No. 86-3157
      - Brooks v. Taylor, No. 86-3160
      - Howard County v. Sentry Ins. Co., No. 86-3166
      - United States v. Bagguley, No. 86-5032; (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 137)
      - United States v. Hill, No. 86-5671
      - Lawson v. Murray, No. 86-6763
      - Lafaut v. Smith, No. 86-7162
      - Hooper v. Garraghty, No. 86-7295
      - Acorn Structures v. Swantz, No. 87-1039
      - Patterson v. Mack Trucks, No. 87-1075
      - Superior Pocahontas Coal Co. v. Island Creek Coal Co., No. 87-1115
      - Dunham v. Marine Transp. Lines, No. 87-1117
      - Pauley v. United Mine Workers Health and Retirement Funds, No. 87-1155
      - Morris v. Bowen, No. 87-1175
      - Arts Festival Ass'n of Atlanta v. Braswell, No. 87-1517
      - Payne v. Oster, No. 87-1567
      - Atlantic Permanent Fed. Sav. and Loan Ass'n v. American Casualty Co., No. 87-1572
      - Austin v. Michelin Ams. Research and Dev. Corp., No. 87-1573
      - Roberts v. Bowen, No. 87-1614 (Box 138)
      - Sattler v. Johnson, No. 87-1632
      - Bundy v. Best Prods. Co., No. 87-1643
      - Hofherr v. Dart Indus., No. 87-1644
      - Bullock Constr. v. Federal Express Corp., No. 87-1662
      - Torney v. Miles, No. 87-1668
      - Byrd v. Gate Petroleum Co., No. 87-1696
      - Levy v. Kindred, No. 87-1698
      - Fickling v. Burger King Corp., No. 87-1725
      - In re McKissick, No. 87-2024
      - Virginia Synod Lutheran Homes v. Baecher, No. 87-2081
      - Allstate Ins. Co. v. Skeeters, No. 87-2102
      - Robertson v. Connors, No. 87-2136
      - Medical & Technical Research Assocs. v. Boyles, No. 87-2546
      - McKenzie v. United States, No. 87-2575
      - Padow v. Commissioner, No. 87-2638
      - McNeal v. United States Steel Mining Co., No. 87-2647
      - Private Ledger Fin. Servs. v. Wright, No. 87-2657
      - Chafin Coal Co. v. United Mine Workers, No. 87-2671
      - Abernathy v. Clarke, No. 87-3055
      - In re H. G. D. & J. Mining Co., No. 87-3511
      - Player v. Maher Terminals, No. 87-3535
      - Sevigny v. Dicksey, No. 87-3550
      - Boyce v. Turner & Newall, Ltd., No. 87-3563 (Box 139)
      - Bernard Johnson, Inc. v. Wood, No. 87-3579
      - Collins v. Sonat Marine, No. 87-3593
      - Harbour v. Commerce Sec. Corp., No. 87-3610
      - Kimbro v. Cordis Corp., No. 87-3736
      - Todd v. Sorrell, No. 87-3806
      - Williams v. Rite Aid Corp., No. 87-3822
      - Jackson v. Volkswagen of Am., No. 87-3823
      - Official Comm. of Equity Sec. Holders v. Mabey, No. 87-3842
      - EPE, Inc. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 87-3850; (2 folders)
      - Aquenergy Sys. v. Federal Energy Regulatory Comm'n, No. 87-3853
      - Bachur v. Democratic Nat'l Party, No. 87-3872(L)
      - Schneider v. Wickes Cos., No. 87-3887
      - United States v. Colvard, No. 87-5028
      - United States v. Jureidini, No. 87-5039 (Box 140)
      - United States v. Wilson, No. 87-5060
      - United States v. Holmes, No. 87-5066
      - United States v. Watts, No. 87-5080
      - United States v. Williams, No. 87-5109
      - United States v. Curtis, No. 87-5110
      - United States v. Stuver, No. 87-5138
      - United States v. Colzie, No. 87-5147
      - United States v. Simmons, No. 87-5526
      - United States v. Tucker, No. 87-5528
      - United States v. Wright, No. 87-5530
      - United States v. Holloman, No. 87-5551
      - United States v. Barata-Jimenez, No. 87-5562
      - United States v. Scruggs, No. 87-5603(L)
      - United States v. Croy, No. 87-5607
      - United States v. Hicks, No. 87-5619
      - United States v. Zebulon, No. 87-5623
      - United States v. Ward, No. 87-5624
      - United States v. Cobb, No. 87-7197
      - Lane v. Griffin, No. 87-7530
      - Monge v. Clark, No. 87-7630
      - United States v. Elliott, No. 87-7712
      - Heritage Village Church and Missionary Fellowship v. United States, No. 88-1559
      - Plyer v. Evatt, No. 88-7511; (2 folders)
    - 1988 October term
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Amason, Inc., No. 84-1561; (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 141)
      - Adkins v. Benefits Review Bd., No. 85-1566
      - American Booksellers Ass'n v. Virginia, No. 85-1961; (3 folders)
      - Andes v. Versant Corp., No. 86-1186
      - Carter v. Bowen, No. 86-1718
      - Redic v. Watts, No. 86-3824; (1 folder) (Box 142)
      - Flat Top Lake Ass'n v. United States, No. 87-1514
      - In re Federal Support Co., No. 87-1695
      - Monarch Ins. Co. v. Prince, No. 87-2122
      - Columbia Gas Transmission Corp. v. Federal Energy Regulatory Comm'n, No. 87-2628
      - Deadwyler v. Volkswagen of Am., No. 87-2688
      - Davis v. McLaughlin, No. 87-3085
      - Minuteman Transit v. Campbell-Taggert, Inc., No. 87-3617
      - Smith v. Nesius, No. 87-3634
      - Jackson v. Bair, No. 87-3827
      - United States v. Berry, No. 87-5583 (Box 143)
      - American States Ins. Co. v. Prozzillo, No. 88-1107
      - Davidson Mining v. Federal Mine Safety & Health Admin., No. 88-1136
      - Bellamy v. City of Loris, No. 88-1301
      - Merchants Bank v. Citizens Sav. and Loan Ass'n, No. 88-1332
      - Erskine v. Union Carbide Corp., No. 88-1366
      - Glenn v. Baluss, No. 88-1710
      - Connors v. New River Co., No. 88-1764
      - Hollerbach v. Fay, No. 88-1792
      - Brock v. Wendell's Woodwork, No. 88-2063
      - Manassas Lumber Corp. v. Sanders Quarry, No. 88-2144
      - Corder v. Teamsters Local Union No. 175, No. 88-2515
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Southern Md. Hosp. Center, No. 88-2614
      - Hendley v. Lee, No. 88-2631
      - Woodall v. Lester, No. 88-2633 (Box 144)
      - Parsons v. West Virginia Works Hourly Employees Pension Plan, No. 88-2649
      - Mammay v. J. Arthur Dosher Memorial Hosp., No. 88-2653
      - Varney v. Bowen, No. 88-2832
      - Crabtree v. Eagle Mfg. Co., No. 88-2833
      - South Carolina Dep't of Wildlife and Marine Resources v. Marsh, No. 88-2840
      - Citizens & S. Nat'l Bank v. Specialty Equip., No. 88-2843
      - Lindenmuth v. Blanton, No. 88-2845
      - Bryant v. Muskin Co., No. 88-2857
      - Joann Coal Co. v. United States, No. 88-2874
      - In re Korf Technologies, No. 88-2886
      - Abbott v. City of Virginia Beach, No. 88-2958
      - Shopco Distrib. Co. v. Commanding Gen., Marine Corps Base, No. 88-2974
      - Gould v. Department of Health and Human Servs., No. 88-3091
      - Chapman v. United States, No. 88-3100
      - Hannan v. Bowen, No. 88-3108
      - Mason & Dixon Lines v. First Nat'l Bank, No. 88-3109
      - Weese v. Nationwide Ins. Co., No. 88-3117 (Box 145)
      - Lowry v. Celotex Corp., No. 88-3135
      - Best Way Distrib. Co. v. Worcester Beer Wholesalers, No. 88-3168
      - Russell v. Chariker, No. 88-3518
      - Dominion Bank, N.A. v. Wilson, No. 88-3577
      - Rom v. Connelly, No. 88-3591
      - Spartan Grain & Mill Co. v. Ralston Purina Co., No. 88-3610
      - Dabbaghian v. Pierce, No. 88-3611
      - Arthur Young & Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 88-3640
      - Marion Space Corp. v. Kroger Co., No. 88-3835
      - Byrd v. International Transtech Corp., No. 88-3847
      - Republican Party v. Martin, No. 88-3862
      - Rhodes Constr. Corp. v. Peoples Plaza W., No. 88-3889
      - Aliff v. Joy Technologies, No. 88-3912
      - Taywood Mining v. Wellman, No. 88-3928
      - Bright v. McClure, No. 88-3974
      - United States v. Machen, No. 88-5012
      - United States v. Cooper, No. 88-5077 (Box 146)
      - United States v. Wright, No. 88-5078
      - United States v. Richardson, No. 88-5116
      - United States v. Fordyce, No. 88-5123
      - United States v. Slatton, No. 88-5129
      - United States v. Jackson, No. 88-5144
      - United States v. Johnson, No. 88-5148
      - United States v. Mills, No. 88-5533
      - United States v. Runnells, No. 88-5555
      - United States v. Johnson, No. 88-5630
      - Milano v. Johnson, No. 88-7237
      - Capitol Credit Plan v. Shaffer, No. 89-8108
    - 1989 October term
      - Patterson v. McLean Credit Union, No. 85-2394; (2 folders)
      - Crabbe v. Troublefield, No. 88-1127
      - W. R. Grace & Co. v. S. C. Loveland Co., No. 88-1311
      - Laurens Elec. Coop. v. Altec Indus., No. 88-1733; (2 folders)
      - Duncan v. United States Dep't of the Army, No. 88-2143 (Box 147)
      - Foremost Guar. Corp. v. Meritor Sav. Bank, No. 88-3163
      - United States v. Mahler, No. 88-5193
      - United States v. Clark, No. 88-5547
      - United States v. Dudley, No. 88-5570
      - Alco Standard Corp. v. Bretner, No. 89-1414
      - Kleemann v. McDonnell Douglas Corp., No. 89-2032(L)
      - J. L. S. Coal Corp. v. Director, Office of Workers' Compensation Programs, No. 89-2037
      - Singh v. Sullivan, No. 89-2641
      - Ethridge v. Lumberman's Mut. Casualty Co., No. 89-2908
      - Belcher v. Oliver, No. 89-2918
    - United States District Court cases
      - Brown v. South Carolina State Bd. of Educ., 1966
      - Dickson v. Sitterson, 1968, (3 folders); (6 folders) (Box 148, Box 149)
      - Heavy Duty Haulers v. United States, 1968, (2 folders) (Box 150)
      - O'Shields v. McNair, 1967, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 151)
      - Woods v. Hanley, 1968
    - Other circuit cases
      - First circuit, 1983
        - United States v. Lopez, No. 82-1184
        - AFM Pilots Ass'n v. AFM Corp., No. 82-1348
        - United States v. Tsopas, No. 82-1645
        - United States v. Hughes Nursing Home, No. 82-1717
        - United States v. Lamare, No. 82-1757
        - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Community Health Servs., No. 82-1821
        - Economic Dev. and Indus. Corp. v. United States, No. 82-1845
        - Luna v. Immigration and Naturalization Serv., No. 82-1863
        - In re Interception of oral communications, No. 82-1881
        - Souza v. Ellerthorpe, No. 82-1936
        - Scuncio Motors v. Subaru, No. 83-1009 (Box 152)
        - Miscellany
      - Second circuit
        - 1983
          - United States v. Farra, No. 83-1262
          - Jacob v. Thomas, No. 83-2161
          - United States v. Tortorello, No. 83-2176
          - Arnold v. Management, Postal Serv., No. 83-6150
          - Dunlop Tire & Rubber v. Interstate Commerce Comm'n, No. 83-6216
          - L & H Vitamins v. J.R. Carlson Laboratories, No. 83-7350
          - Kelley v. Lawyers, City of N.Y., No. 83-7438
          - Temple v. Anthony B. Cassedy and Assocs., No. 83-7469
          - Copley v. Morality in Media, No. 83-7484
          - Bertani v. Consolidated Rail Corp., No. 83-7500
        - 1984
          - United States v. Moyles, No. 83-1211
          - Industria Arredamenti Fratelli Saporiti v. Craig, No. 83-7454
          - Fennell v. Warner-Lambert Co., No. 83-7473
          - L. G., Inc. v. Sullivan, No. 83-7493
          - Cohen v. Board of Educ., Smithtown Cent. School, No. 83-7513
          - Walter E. Heller & Co. v. Video Innovations, No. 83-7568
          - Vinieris v. Byzantine Maritime Corp., No. 83-7574
        - Miscellany, 1983-1984 (Box 153)